You know what I think? Besides the fact that I look like I'm like 17 and trying to figure out
if I want to play basketball next season, I feel like that's like my look right now.
I think that the effort to dismantle community, which ultimately ends up being more effective
and powerful than our government in supporting us and protecting us, et cetera, has also come
through in very subliminal ways that we now continue to perpetuate. So this idea of don't
care about other people's fate when you can't control their fate, I think that that really
comes from, again, this colonialist individualism idea that it's like, all I got to do is worry
about me. When ultimately, in a community, yes, you need to ultimately be concerned about
how you show up in that community. But part of how you show up in that community is by
considering other people and how you show up as a resource, like how you show up as a support
of resources, et cetera. And if you ultimately feel like nothing I do can change other people's
fate, then you're not even going to concern yourself with how you show up in those ways.
And then you're going to say, well, that's what the government's supposed to do. And the government
is like, I mean, honestly, I don't care about none of y'all. And then the government looks at you like,
how dare you consider us to be the resource for that? Even though there has been a concerted effort
to undermine community as an effort. Legislation disrupts community all the time. Policing disrupts
community. I mean, I saw a story the other day of this woman saying that she became radicalized when
she lived in a housing project and her mom had started a garden in the project. And that garden
was meant to not only provide fruits and vegetables for the community, but also it gave the kids something
to do. It gave them something to learn, et cetera. And then people from the housing authority came,
uprooted the garden, poured bleach on the soil so that it couldn't be used. And she was like,
that was when I became radicalized. Ultimately, community should not be a radical thought.
Humans are a herd species. So it's actually our most natural and organic way of being.
It's actually our most natural it makes it